<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> <rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://local-acdis/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"> <channel> <title>Radio Podcast Feed</title>
 <description>During each ACDIS Radio show, Brian Murphy and a co-host chat with a special guest including industry leaders, ACDIS advisory board members, physicians and physician advisors, and CDI managers and specialists. You&#039;ll hear about best practices, tips, and the latest ACDIS and CDI-related healthcare news. This lively 30 minute program will keep CDI and HIM professionals entertained and up-to-date on the pulse of the CDI industry.
Tune in every other Wednesday at 11:30 a.m. ET</description>
 <link>https://local-acdis/</link>
 <atom:link rel="self" href="https://local-acdis/podcast.rss" />
 <language>en</language>
 <image> <url>https://acdis.org/sites/acdis/themes/acdis/release/images/acdis.png</url>
 <title>Radio Podcast Feed</title>
 <link>https://local-acdis/</link>
</image>
 <itunes:subtitle>Keeping you up-to-date on all things CDI</itunes:subtitle>
 <itunes:summary>Join ACDIS Director Brian Murphy every other Wednesday for ACDIS Radio, a bi-weekly talk show covering the hottest topics in CDI.</itunes:summary>
 <itunes:category text="Education" />
 <itunes:image href="https://acdis.org/sites/acdis/themes/acdis/release/images/acdis.png" />
 <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
 <item> <title>ACDIS conference preview: Mortality scores and quality data</title>
 <link>https://local-acdis/acdis-radio/acdis-conference-preview-mortality-scores-and-quality-data</link>
 <description>With special guest Susan Schmitz, JD, RN, CCS, CCDS, CDIP, Regional Director of Clinical Documentation Improvement for SCAL Kaiser Permanente in Pasadena, California. Co-hosted by Allen Frady, RN, BSN, CCDS, CCS, CDI Education Specialist for ACDIS. 

To read the 2019 Medicare Advantage and Part D Rate Announcement and Call Letter as featured on &quot;In the News,&quot; please click here.

To learn more about the 11th annual ACDIS conference and 10 reasons to attend, please click here.
</description>
 <enclosure url="http://file-examples.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/file_example_MP4_480_1_5MG.mp4" length="1570024" type="video/mp4" />
 <guid isPermaLink="false">13362</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 12:32:02 -0400</pubDate>
 <source url="https://local-acdis/podcast.rss">Radio Podcast Feed</source>
 <itunes:duration>32:15</itunes:duration>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
